Guide to the Tremont Despatch and United States Mail Coach waybills, 1839-1841.
Tremont Despatch and United States Mail Coach waybills
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Tremont Despatch and United States Mail Coach waybills, 1839-1841.
4778
Tremont Despatch and United States Mail Coach.
.1 cubic feet.
Manuscripts
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Waybills from Boston and Lowell to Brattleborough and Keene; from Boston to Lexington, Concord, and Harvard; and from Brattleborough and Keene to Lowell and Boston, 1839-1841.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Waybills from Boston and Lowell to Brattleborough and Keene; from Boston to Lexington, Concord, and Harvard; and from Brattleborough and Keene to Lowell and Boston, 1839-1841.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Tremont Despatch and United States Mail Coach.
Subjects:
Railroads--Massachusetts--Boston.
Form and Genre Terms:
Waybills.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Boston and Lowell to Keene and Brattleborough. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1839 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Boston and Lowell to Keene and Brattleborough. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1839-1840 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Boston and Lowell to Keene and Brattleborough. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1839-1841 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Boston and Lowell to Keene and Brattleborough. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1840 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Boston and Lowell to Keene and Brattleborough. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1840-1841 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Boston and Lowell to Keene and Brattleborough. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1841 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Boston and Lowell to Keene and Brattleborough. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1841 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Boston to Lexington, Concord and Harvard. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1841 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Brattleborough and Keene to Boston and Lowell. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1840-1841 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Brattleborough and Keene to Boston and Lowell. Way Bills. Massachusetts Railroad, 1841 (Box 1, Folder 10)